digitaltriggers.io 2015-12-10

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy will help serve to explain:

  * What information we collect and why we collect it.
  * How we utilize that information
  * The choices we offer, including how to access and update information

By visiting this Website and requesting information, products or services offered on or through this Website, you agree to the terms of the Privacy Policy, as they may be amended from time to time. As the Company updates or expands its Website, services or products, the Privacy Policy may change and the changes are effective upon posting. Please check back frequently for Privacy

Policy updates, as it is the sole responsibility of the user to be aware of changes. Other than posting the changes to the Website, the Company does not provide any notice of change in any manner. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, the Website Terms and Conditions which govern your use of this Website in general.

This Website is intended for users who are located in the United States of America. The Privacy Policy shall be interpreted under the laws of the United States.

By offering Personal Information about yourself on our website, or in the course of using our services, you consent to the transfer of your Personal Information, and any other data we acquire about you from third-party service providers for commercial use.

#### **Information We Collect**

  1. Details of your visits to our website and the resources that you access, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data.
  2. Information that you provide by filling in forms on our website, such as when you sign up to our newsletter, register for information or make a purchase.
  3. Information provided to us when you communicate with us for any reason.
  4. Your name and job title.
  5. Contact information including an email address.
  6. Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests.
  7. Other information relevant to customer surveys and or/offers.

Additional types of information that may be collected include:

_Third Party Information_. Company may collect Personal Information from you when you provide information to a third party and Company subsequently acquires or uses the information provided by the third party. Such information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and such other information you may have provided to the third party. When acquiring this information, Company seeks assurances from the third party that you agreed to provide and have such information acquired by Company. If you did not give express permission, or you would like to remove your permission, you may suppress all of your information by sending notification to us.

_IP Addresses_. Company automatically tracks certain information based upon your behavior on the site. We may use this information to do internal research on our users’ demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on the site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on the site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address. Your Internet Protocol (“IP”) is a unique Internet “address” which is assigned to you by your Internet Service Provider (“ISP”). For local area network (“LAN”), DSL, or cable modem users, an IP address may be permanently assigned to a particular computer. IP addresses are automatically logged by Web servers, collecting information about a user’s traffic patterns. While the IP address does not identify an individual by name, it may, with the cooperation of the ISP, be used to locate and identify an individual using the Web. Your IP address can, however, reveal what geographic area you are connecting from, or which ISP you are using. Finally, other websites you visit have IP addresses, and we may collect the IP addresses of those websites and their pages.

_Credit Card Information and Bank Account Information_. Company may, in certain instances, collect credit card numbers, bank account information and related information when an individual places an order on Company’s Website. When the credit card or bank account information is submitted to Company, such information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. Company will use the credit card information or bank account information for purposes of processing and completing the transaction you requested on the Website, and the credit card information or bank account information will be disclosed to third parties as necessary to complete the requested purchase transaction.

#### **Use of Cookies**

On occasion, we may gather information about your computer for our services and to provide statistical information regarding the use of our website to our advertisers. Such information will not identify you personally it is statistical data about our visitors and their use of our site. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever.

Similarly to the above, we may gather information about your general internet use by using a cookie file. A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

All computers have the ability to automatically accept or decline cookies. This can be done by activating the setting on your browser which determines how to deal with cookies. Please note that should you choose to decline cookies, you may be unable to access particular parts of our website.

Our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control. Such cookies (if used) would be downloaded once you click on advertisements on our website.

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that website.

#### **Use of Your Information**

The information that we collect and store relating to you is primarily used to enable us to provide our services to you. In addition, we may use the information for the following purposes:

  1. To provide you with information requested from us, relating to our products or services. To provide information on other products which we feel may be of interest to you, where you have consented to receive such information.
  2. To meet our contractual commitments to you.
  3. To notify you about any changes to our website, such as improvements or service/product changes, that may affect our service.
  4. Internal record keeping.
  5. To improve our products and services.
  6. To periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you provided.
  7. To contact you for market research purposes.

If you are an existing customer, we may contact you with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you.

Further, we may use your data so that you can be provided with information about unrelated goods and services which we consider may be of interest to you. We may contact you about these goods and services by any of the methods that you consented at the time your information was collected.

If you are a new customer, we will only contact you or allow third parties to contact you only when you have provided consent and only by those means you provided consent for.

If you do not want us to use your data for our or third parties you will have the opportunity to withhold your consent to this when you provide your details to us on the form on which we collect your data.

Please be advised that we do not reveal information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers but we may, on occasion, provide them with aggregate statistical information about our visitors.

If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at anytime by writing to, or emailing us at privacy@myadwordsaudit.com.

You are entitled to request details of your personal information which we hold under the Data Protection Act of 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email the aforementioned address.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is inaccurate or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

#### **Storing Your Personal Data**

Data that is provided to us is stored on our secure servers. Details relating to any transactions entered into on our site will be encrypted to ensure its safety.

The transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and therefore we cannot guarantee the security of data sent to us electronically and transmission of such data is therefore entirely at your own risk. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password so that you can access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential.

#### **Remarketing and Internet-based Ads**

– Third party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites on the internet.

– Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our Website.

– Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page ([http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)), or you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page ([http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp))

#### **Disclosing Your Information**

Where applicable, we may disclose your personal information to any member of our group. This includes, where applicable, our subsidiaries, our holding company and its other subsidiaries (if any).

We may also disclose your personal information to third parties:

  1. Where we sell any or all of our business and/or our assets to a third party.
  2. Where we are legally required to disclose your information.
  3. To assist fraud protection and minimize credit risk.

#### **Third Party Links**

You might find links to third party websites on our website. These websites should have their own privacy policies which you should check. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies whatsoever as we have no control over them.

#### **Access To Information**

Should you wish to receive details that we hold about you please contact us using the contact details below.

Company provides you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when it asks for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference by emailing or calling us per the information contained on our contact page.

If you no longer wish to receive our promotions, you may opt-out of receiving it by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing or calling us per the information contained on our contact page.

#### **Contacting Us**

We welcome any questions, comments or requests you may have regarding this Privacy Policy. Please do not hesitate to contact us atprivacy@web1syndication.com.

#### **Consent**

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of information as outlined in the above, documented Policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
